19th and 20th century Architecture Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
19th and 20th century Architecture Lantern Slide Collection
1900-1960
VRC 2005
Yale University Arts Library
32
96 boxes
Collection consists of black and white glass lantern slides of modern architecture, predominantly European.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of black and white glass lantern slides of modern architecture, predominantly European.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by country. Further sub-divided by city or other location and building type or name.
Architecture, Modern -- 19th century; Architecture, Modern -- 20th Century; Slides; Lantern slides; Reproductions
- Africa (Box 1)
  - Accra, Ghana (Box 1)
  - Algiers, Algeria (Box 1)
  - Carthage, Tunisia (Box 1)
  - Casablanca (Box 1)
  - Nemours (Box 1)
  - Rabat, Morocco (Box 1)
  - S. Charles Basilica (Box 1)
  - Tripoli, Libya (Box 1)
- Australia (Box 1)
  - Adelaide (Box 1)
  - Brisbane (Box 1)
  - Canberra (Box 1)
  - Melbourne (Box 1)
  - Sydney (Box 1)
- Austria (Box 1)
  - Architects (Box 1)
    - Various (Box 1)
    - Loos, Adolf, 1870-1933 (Box 1–2)
    - Wagner, Otto, 1841-1918 (Box 2)
  - Cities (Box 2)
    - Hirschegg (Box 2)
    - Linz (Box 2)
    - Modling, Vienna (Box 2)
    - Payerbach (Box 2)
    - Salzburg (Box 2)
    - Vienna (Box 2)
      - Churches (Box 2)
        - Steinhofkirche (Lunatic Asyl.) (Box 2)
        - Votive Church (Box 2)
      - Exchanges (Box 2)
        - Bourse (Box 2)
      - Exhibitions (Box 2)
      - Gates (Box 2)
      - Government Buildings (Box 2)
        - Arsenal (Box 2)
        - House of Lord, (Project) (Box 2)
        - Imperial Forum (Box 2)
        - Landstandeshaus (Box 2)
        - Mint (Box 2)
        - Palace of Justice (Box 2)
        - Paliament Building (Box 2)
        - Postal Savings Bank (Box 2)
        - Rathaus (Box 2)
      - Hospitals (Box 2)
      - Hotels (Box 2)
      - Houses- Apartments (Box 3)
      - Houses- Residences (Box 3)
        - Moller House (Box 3)
        - Scheu (Box 3)
        - Steiner House (Box 3)
        - Strasser House (Box 3)
        - Wagner Villa (Box 3)
      - Housing (Box 3)
        - Friedrich Austerlitz (Box 3)
        - Fuchsenfeldhof Housing (Box 3)
        - Heiligenstadt Housing (Box 3)
        - Lindenhof Housing (Box 3)
        - Oberkirchgasse Housing (Box 3)
        - Quarin-Hof (Box 3)
        - Reumanhof Housing (Box 4)
        - Sandleiten Housing (Box 4)
        - Werkbund (Box 4)
        - Wienerberg Housing (Box 4)
      - Libraries (Box 4)
      - Museums (Box 4)
        - Secession Building (Box 4)
      - Palaces (Box 4)
      - Recreation (Box 4)
      - Restaurants (Box 4)
      - Schools (Box 4)
      - Stations (Box 4)
      - Stores (Box 4)
        - Goldman and Salatsch Building (Box 4)
      - Theaters (Box 4)
        - Hofburg Theater (Box 4)
- Belgium (Box 4)
  - General (Box 4)
    - Horta, Victor (Box 4)
    - Van De Velde, Henri (Box 4)
  - Cities (Box 4)
    - Antwerp (Box 4)
      - Guiette House (Box 4)
    - Brussels (Box 5)
      - Exchanges (Box 5)
        - Bourse (Box 5)
      - Exhibitions (Box 5)
        - World's Fair 1935 (Box 5)
        - World Exposition 1958 (Box 5)
          - French Pavilion (Box 5)
          - Norwegian Pavilion (Box 5)
          - Spanish Pavilion (Box 5)
          - West Germany Pavilion (Box 5)
      - Government Buildings (Box 5)
        - Palais de Justice (Box 5)
      - Hotels (Box 5)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 5)
        - Canneel House (Box 5)
        - Solvay Residence (Box 5)
        - Stoclet House (Box 5)
        - Tassel House (Box 5)
      - Monasteries (Box 5)
        - Visitation Monastery (Box 5)
      - Office Buildings (Box 5)
        - Maison du Peuple (Box 5)
      - Palaces (Box 5)
      - Stores (Box 5)
      - Theaters (Box 6)
    - Ghent (Box 6)
    - Uccle (Box 6)
- Britain (Box 6)
  General
  [Boxes 6-33]
  - General (Box 6)
    - Churches (Box 6)
    - Houses (Box 6)
    - Housing (Box 6)
    - Interiors (Box 6)
    - Planning (Box 6)
    - Schools (Box 7)
    - Taverns (Box 7)
    - Toll Gates (Box 7)
  - Architects (Box 7)
    - Various (Box 7)
    - Aiken, Edward, 1780-1820 (Box 7)
    - Archigram (Box 7)
    - Architects Coop. Partnership (Box 7)
    - Baillie Scott, M.H. (Box 7)
    - Baxter, Arthur (Box 7)
    - Boulfon (Box 7)
    - Buckingham, James Silk (Box 7)
    - Burges, William, 1827-1881 (Box 7)
    - Busby, C.A. (Box 7)
    - Carpenter, R.C. (Box 7)
    - Cook, Peter (Box 7)
    - Eastlake, Charles (Box 7)
    - Fairbarn, Williams (Box 7)
    - Fry, E. Maxwell (Box 7)
    - Gandy, Joseph M. (Box 7)
    - Goodwin, Edward William (Box 7)
    - Goodwin, Francis (Box 8)
    - Gibson, Robert (Box 8)
    - Gray, Eileen (Box 8)
    - Heron, Ron (Box 8)
    - Howard, Ebenezer (Box 8)
    - Hughes, John A. (Box 8)
    - Hunt, T.F. (Box 8)
    - Jellicoe, G.A. (Box 8)
    - Jones, Owen (Box 8)
    - Kendall, H.E. (Box 8)
    - Lamb, E. B. (Box 8)
    - Lancaster, Osbert (Box 8)
    - Loudon, John C. (Box 8)
      - Loudon's Encyclopaedia (Box 8)
    - Lugar, Robert (Box 9)
    - Mackintosh, Charles Rennie (Box 9)
    - Matheson, Ewing (Box 9)
    - Middleton (Box 9)
    - Mitchell, Robert (Box 9)
    - Nash, John (Box 9)
    - Nightingale, Florence (Box 9)
    - Own, Robert (Box 9)
    - Papworth, J.B. (Box 9)
    - Papworth, Wyatt (Box 9)
    - Parker, Charles (Box 9)
    - Payne, Alexander (Box 9)
    - Pugin, A. Welby (Box 9)
    - Pocock, W.I. (Box 9)
    - Randall, James (Box 9)
    - Reilly, Sir Charles (Box 9)
    - Repton, Humphrey (Box 9)
    - Robinson, P.F. (Box 9)
    - Scott, Sir George Gilbert, 1811-1878 (Box 9)
    - Scott, William (Box 9)
    - Shaw, Norman (Box 9)
    - Slater, William (Box 10)
    - Smirke, Sydney (Box 10)
    - Smithson, Peter (Box 10)
    - Soane, Sir John (Box 10)
    - Stirling, James (Box 10)
    - Street, George (Box 10)
    - Thomson, J. (Box 10)
    - Towsend, C.H. (Box 10)
    - Voysey, C.F.A. (Box 10)
    - Walton, George (Box 10)
    - Watt (Box 10)
    - Webb, Philip (Box 10)
    - Wilkinson (Box 10)
    - Wilson, C.H. (Box 10)
  - Places (Box 10)
    - Abbotsford (Box 10)
    - Aberyswith (Box 10)
    - Adcote (Box 10)
    - Aldwark (Box 10)
    - Alton Towers (Box 10)
    - Ardossan (Box 10)
    - Ascot (Box 10)
    - Ashburnham Park (Box 10)
    - Ashridge Park (Box 10)
    - Aycliffe (Box 10)
    - Barbacombe, Devon (Box 10)
    - Bagby (Box 10)
    - Baldersby (Box 11)
    - Balmoral Castle (Box 11)
    - Barrow in Furnees (Box 11)
    - Barton St. Mary (Box 11)
    - Bath (Box 11)
    - Baughurstm Hampshire (Box 11)
    - Becontree (Box 11)
    - Bedford Park (Box 11)
    - Belvoir Castle (Box 11)
    - Bexley Heath (Box 11)
    - Bexhill-on-Sea (Box 11)
    - Bexton Croft (Box 11)
    - Birkenhead (Box 11)
    - Birmingham (Box 11)
    - Blackpool (Box 11)
    - Blackwells (Box 11)
    - Blaise Hamlet (Box 11)
    - Bottisham (Box 11)
    - Bournville (Box 11)
    - Bradfield (Box 12)
    - Bradford (Box 12)
    - Brighton (Box 12)
      - Churches (Box 12)
    - Bristol (Box 12)
    - Britannia Tubular Bridge (Box 12)
    - Broadleys on Lake Windemere (Box 12)
    - Bryanston (Box 12)
    - Burtnhamoncrouch (Box 12)
    - Bushey (Box 12)
    - Cambridge (Box 12)
      - Houses (Box 12)
      - Residences (Box 12)
      - Libraries (Box 12)
      - Museums (Box 12)
        - Fitzwilliam Museum (Box 12)
      - Railroad Stations (Box 13)
      - Schools (Box 13)
        - History Faculty (Box 13)
    - Camden Town (Box 13)
    - Canterbury (Box 13)
    - Cardiff (Box 13)
    - Castell Coch (Box 13)
    - Castle Morton (Box 13)
    - Caterham (Box 13)
    - Chatsworth (Box 13)
    - Cheadle (Box 13)
    - Cheddar Gorge (Box 13)
    - Cheltenham (Box 13)
    - Chertsey (Box 13)
    - Cheshire (Box 14)
    - Chester (Box 14)
    - Chichester (Box 14)
    - Chorley Wood (Box 14)
    - Churt (Box 14)
    - Claremont (Box 14)
    - Coalbrookdale (Box 14)
    - Coalpit Heath (Box 14)
    - Cobham Surney (Box 14)
    - Colchester (Box 14)
    - Colharbour Wood (Hants) (Box 14)
    - Colwall (Box 14)
    - Cork (Box 14)
    - Cove (Box 14)
    - Coventry (Box 14)
    - Cowley Manor (Box 14)
    - Crawley (Box 14)
    - Crew Hall (Box 14)
    - Cronkhill (Box 14)
    - Croydon (Box 14)
    - Cumbernauld (Box 14)
    - Dagenham (Box 14)
    - Darlington (Box 14)
    - Dartmouth (Box 14)
    - Deptford (Box 14)
    - Derby (Box 14)
    - Devonport (Box 14)
    - Dodington House (Box 15)
    - Dorking (Box 15)
    - Dropmore, Buckinghanshire (Box 15)
    - Dublin (Box 15)
    - Duff House (Box 15)
    - Dunston (Box 15)
    - Durham (Box 15)
    - Ealing (Box 15)
    - East Grinstead (Box 15)
    - East Kilbridge (Box 15)
    - East Knoyle (Box 15)
    - Eatington Park (Box 15)
    - Eaton Hall, Cheshire (Box 15)
    - Edensor (Box 15)
    - Egebaston (Box 15)
    - Edinburgh (Box 15)
      - Churches (Box 15)
      - Monuments (Box 15)
      - Schools (Box 16)
    - Edgham, Surrey (Box 16)
    - Exeter (Box 16)
    - Essex (Box 16)
    - Ewhurst (Box 16)
    - Exmouth (Box 16)
    - Farham Common (Box 16)
    - Five Gables (Box 16)
    - Folkestone (Box 16)
    - Fonthill Abbey (Box 16)
    - Fordingbridge (Box 16)
    - Frinton-on-Sea (Box 16)
    - Fulbourne (Box 16)
    - Fullbrook House (Box 16)
    - Fulham (Box 16)
    - Garth (Box 16)
    - Glasgow (Box 16)
      - Houses (Box 16)
      - Restaurants (Box 16)
        - Craston Tea Room (Box 16)
        - Willow Tea Rooms (Box 16)
      - Schools (Box 16)
    - Goddards (Box 16)
    - Gospel Oak (Box 16)
    - Gosport (Box 16)
    - Grange House (Box 16)
    - Great Kimble (Box 16)
    - Greathirkleby (Box 17)
    - Greenwich (Box 17)
    - Greyfriars (Box 17)
    - Grey Walls (Box 17)
    - Groombridge (Box 17)
    - Hahfax (Box 17)
    - Halland (Box 17)
    - Hampstead Garden Suburbs (Box 17)
    - Halwel (Box 17)
    - Harlow New Town (Box 17)
    - Hatfield (Box 17)
    - Harrow (Box 17)
    - Healey (Box 17)
    - Heathcote (Box 17)
    - Helensburgh (Box 17)
    - Hindenton (Box 17)
    - Holt (Box 17)
    - Hopedene (Box 17)
    - Huddersfield (Box 17)
    - Hughenden (Box 17)
    - Hunstanton (Box 18)
    - Ickworth (Box 18)
    - Isle of Wight (Box 18)
    - Kendal, Westmorland (Box 18)
    - Kew (Box 18)
    - Kilmacolm (Box 18)
    - Kinmel Park (Box 18)
    - Knightshays (Box 18)
    - Lansing, Sussex (Box 18)
    - Leeds (Box 18)
    - Leadeameroch (Box 18)
    - Leek (Box 18)
    - Leicester (Box 18)
    - Leith (Box 18)
    - Letchworth Gardens (Box 18)
    - Lismore Castle (Box 18)
    - Little Thakeham (Box 19)
    - Liverpool (Box 19)
      - Churches (Box 19)
        - Cathedral (Box 19)
          - Exterior (Box 19)
          - Interior (Box 19)
        - St. Clare's Church (Box 19)
      - Government Buildings (Box 19)
        - S. George's Hall (Box 19)
      - Housing (Box 19)
      - Libraries (Box 19)
      - Office Buildings (Box 19)
      - Schools (Box 19)
        - University of Liverpool (Box 19)
      - Warehouses (Box 19)
    - London (Box 19)
      - Plans & Planning (Box 19)
        - 1937 M.A.R.S. Plan (Box 19)
        - 1944 Greater London Plan (Box 19)
        - 1959 Barlican Redevelopment (Box 20)
      - General Views (Box 20)
        - Streets (Box 20)
        - Arches (Box 20)
      - Banks (Box 20)
        - Bank of England (Box 20)
          - Exterior (Box 20)
          - Interior (Box 20)
          - Soane's Sketches (Box 20)
      - Bridges (Box 20)
      - Churches [boxes 20-22] (Box 20)
        - All Saint's (Box 21)
        - All Soul's Church (Box 21)
        - Hanover Chapel (Box 21)
        - Holy Trinity (Sloan St.) (Box 21)
        - S. Alban's (Holborn) (Box 21)
        - S. Augustine's (Kilburn) (Box 21)
        - S. Chad's (Haggerton) (Box 21)
        - S. Columba (Kingsland Rd.) (Box 21)
        - S. George Cathedral, 1841 (Box 21)
        - S. James The Less (Box 21)
        - S. James Holloway (Box 21)
        - S. John Evangelist (Box 21)
        - S. Martin's (Box 21)
        - S. Matthias (Stoke Newington) (Box 21)
        - S. Pancras Church (Box 21)
        - S. Stephen's (Hampstead) (Box 22)
        - Weigh House Chapel (Box 22)
        - Westminster Abbey (Box 22)
        - Westminster Cathedral (Box 22)
      - Clubs (Box 22)
      - Exhibitions (Box 22)
        - Alexandra Hall (Box 22)
        - Crystal Palace Exhibition (Box 22)
        - Festival of Britain, 1951 (Box 22)
      - Fountains (Box 22)
      - Government Buildings (Box 22)
        - Adelaide Building (Box 22)
        - County Council Buildings (Box 23)
        - County Fire Office (Box 23)
        - County Hall (Box 23)
        - Customs House (Box 23)
        - Duchy of Cornwall Office (Box 23)
        - Foreign Office (Box 23)
        - Law Courts (Box 23)
          - Law Courts Competition (Box 23)
          - Law Courts as Built (G.E. Street) (Box 23)
          - Law Courts at Westminster (Box 23)
          - New Zealand Chambers (Box 23)
        - Parliament (Box 23)
          - Exterior (Box 23)
          - Interior (Box 23)
        - Privy Counsil (Box 23)
        - Scotland Yard (Box 23)
        - Treasury Offices (Box 23)
        - U.S. Embassy (Box 23)
        - Whitehall (War Offices) (Box 24)
      - Hospitals (Box 24)
        - Various (Box 24)
        - Christ's (Box 24)
        - Children's Hospital (Box 24)
        - Finsbury Health Center (Box 24)
        - National Hospital (Box 24)
        - Pioneer Health Center (Box 24)
        - Royal Masonic Hospital (Box 24)
        - S. Bartholomew's Hospital (Box 24)
        - S. Luke's (Box 24)
      - Hotels (Box 24)
        - Langham Hotel (Box 24)
        - Westminster Hotel (Box 24)
      - House- Apartments (Box 24)
        - Albert Hall Apartment (Box 24)
        - Carlenton House Terrace (Box 24)
        - Devonshire House (Box 24)
        - Dorchester House (Box 24)
        - Eaton Mansions (Box 24)
        - Highpoint Apartments Highgate (Box 24)
        - Lawn Road (Box 24)
        - Lowneles Square (Box 24)
        - Mt. Royal Flats (Box 24)
        - Palace Gate Flat (Box 24)
        - Pelham Crescentv (Box 25)
        - Royal Crescent (Box 25)
        - Sassoon House (Box 25)
      - House-Residences (Box 25)
        - Various (Box 25)
        - Bridgewater House (Box 25)
        - William Borges House (Box 25)
        - Denn Levy House (Box 25)
        - Lord Carlisle House (Box 25)
        - Cheyne House (Box 25)
        - Chelsea House (Box 25)
        - Frognal Way House (Box 25)
        - E. Long (Box 25)
        - Sambourne House (Box 25)
        - Soane House (Box 25)
        - Stanmore Hall (Box 25)
        - Old Shan House (Box 25)
      - Housing (Box 25)
        - Roehampton Apartments (Box 25)
      - Industrial Buildings (Box 26)
      - Libraries (Box 26)
      - Monuments (Box 26)
        - Albert Memorial (Box 26)
        - Artillery Memorial (Box 26)
        - Nelson Column (Box 26)
      - Museums (Box 26)
        - British Museum (Box 26)
        - Dulwich Gallery (Box 26)
        - Egyptian Hall Piccadilly (Box 26)
        - Fine Art Society (Box 26)
        - Grosvenor Gallery (Box 26)
        - Marlborough House (Box 26)
        - National Gallery (Box 26)
        - Natural History Museum (Box 26)
        - Soane Museum (Box 26)
        - Tate Gallery (Box 26)
        - Victoria and Albert Museum (Box 26)
      - Office Buildings (Box 26)
        - Brittanic House (Box 26)
        - Daily Express Office (Box 26)
        - Economist Buildings (Box 26)
        - Empire Tea Building (Box 26)
        - Italian State Tourist Department (Box 26)
        - Leith House (Box 26)
        - Victoria House (Box 26)
      - Palaces (Box 26)
        - Buckingham Palace (Box 26)
      - Parks (Box 27)
        - Regent's Park (Box 27)
          - Various (Box 27)
          - Chester Terrace (Box 27)
          - Cumberland Terrace (Box 27)
      - Schools (Box 27)
        - Bishopsgate Institute (Box 27)
        - University College (Box 27)
        - University of London (Box 27)
      - Squares (Box 27)
      - Stations (Box 27)
        - Charing Cross Station (Box 27)
        - Euston Station (Box 27)
        - King's Cross-Station (Box 27)
        - Liverpool Station (Box 27)
        - Nine Elms Goods Stations (Box 27)
        - Paddington Station (Box 28)
        - St. Pancras Station (Box 28)
      - Stores (Box 28)
        - Various (Box 28)
        - Billingsgate Fish Market (Box 28)
        - Peter Jones Store (Box 28)
        - Smithfield Meat Market (Box 28)
      - Theaters (Box 28)
        - Various (Box 28)
        - Pantheon (Box 28)
        - Queen's Hall (Box 28)
      - Warehouses (Box 28)
      - Zoos (Box 28)
    - Luscomee (Box 28)
    - Malton (Box 28)
    - Manchester (Box 28)
      - Government Buildings (Box 28)
        - Old Town Hall (Box 29)
        - Town Hall Designs (Box 29)
      - Houses (Box 29)
      - Museums (Box 29)
      - Schools (Box 29)
      - Stations (Box 29)
      - Warehouses (Box 29)
    - Marshcourt (Box 29)
    - Melksham, Wilts (Box 29)
    - Merton Abbey (Box 29)
    - Michel Grove (Box 29)
    - Middlebrough (Box 29)
    - Millers Dale (Box 29)
    - Millmead (Box 29)
    - Milton Ernest Hall (Box 29)
    - Newbury (Box 29)
    - New Castle-on-Tyne (Box 29)
    - Nitshill (Box 29)
    - Norris Castle (Box 29)
    - Isla of Wight (Box 29)
    - Norney House (Box 29)
    - Northallerton (Box 29)
    - Northampton (Box 29)
    - Norwich (Box 30)
    - Nottingham (Box 30)
    - Oldham (Box 30)
    - Oxford (Box 30)
    - Pangbourne (Box 30)
    - Papillon Hall (Box 30)
    - Parkside (Box 30)
    - Pendlebury (Box 30)
    - Plaistow (Box 30)
    - Plymouth (Box 30)
    - Port Sunlight (Box 30)
    - Preston (Box 30)
    - Prestwood (Box 31)
    - Ramsgate (Box 31)
    - Rreading (Box 31)
    - Richmond (Box 31)
    - Ripon (Box 31)
    - Rockingham (Box 31)
    - Roseneath (Box 31)
    - Roscommon (Box 31)
    - Rotherfield (Box 31)
    - Rugby (Box 31)
    - Saffron Walden (Box 31)
    - Salisbury (Box 31)
    - Saltaire (Box 31)
    - Sandy Lodge (Box 31)
    - Scarborough (Box 31)
    - Scarisbrick Hall (Box 31)
    - Sezincote (Box 31)
    - Sheffield (Box 31)
    - Shrublands (Box 31)
    - Southend-on-Sea (Box 31)
    - Springcot (Box 31)
    - Stevenage (Box 31)
    - Staines (Box 31)
    - Stockwell (Box 31)
    - Stoke Poges Park (Box 31)
    - Stratford-on-Avon (Box 31)
    - Strawberry Hill (Box 31)
    - Streatham (Box 32)
    - Stroud Valley (Box 32)
    - Swanscombe (Box 32)
    - Tangley Manor (Box 32)
    - Taymouth Castle (Box 32)
    - Tigbourne Court (Box 32)
    - Tisbury (Box 32)
    - Toddington Manor (Box 32)
    - Todmorden (Box 32)
    - Trevista Houses (Box 32)
    - Truro (Box 32)
    - Tyringham (Box 32)
    - Uxbridge (Box 32)
    - Waddesdon Manor (Box 32)
    - Wakefield (Box 32)
    - Walton-on-Thames (Box 32)
    - Wantage (Box 32)
    - Watford (Box 32)
    - Welwyn Garden City (Box 32)
    - Wembly (Box 32)
    - West Hartlepool (Box 32)
    - Whipsnade (Box 32)
    - Wilton (Box 33)
    - Wimbledon (Box 33)
    - Winchester (Box 33)
    - Windsor (Box 33)
    - Woneresh (Box 33)
    - Woodhead (Box 33)
    - Woolwich (Box 33)
    - Yarmouth (Box 33)
    - York (Box 33)
- China (Box 33)
  - Various (Box 33)
- Czechoslovakia (Box 33)
  - Various (Box 33)
  - Brno (Box 33)
  - Lidice (Box 33)
  - Pilsen (Box 33)
  - Prague (Box 33)
    - Muller House (Box 33)
- Denmark (Box 33)
  - Aarlus (Box 33)
  - Copenhagen (Box 33)
    - General (Box 33)
    - Planning (Box 34)
    - Airport (Box 34)
    - Churches (Box 34)
      - Chapel & Crematorium (Box 34)
      - Frauen Kirche (Box 34)
      - Grundtvings Church (Box 34)
    - Gates (Box 34)
    - Government Buildings (Box 34)
      - Old Court House (Box 34)
      - Police Station (Box 34)
      - Rathaus (Box 34)
      - Rodovre Town Hall (Box 34)
    - Hospitals (Box 34)
    - Houses- Apartments (Box 34)
    - Housing (Box 34)
    - Museums (Box 34)
      - NY Carlsberg Glyptothek (Box 34)
      - Thor Waldsen Museum (Box 34)
    - Office Buildings (Box 35)
    - Railroad Stations (Box 35)
    - Theaters (Box 35)
      - Tivoli Concert Hall (Box 35)
  - Gentofte (Box 35)
  - Soholm (Box 35)
  - Sollerod (Box 35)
  - Suinninge (Box 35)
- Egypt (Box 35)
  - Alexandria (Box 35)
  - Cairo (Box 35)
- Finland (Box 35)
  - Architects (Box 35)
    - Various (Box 35)
    - Aalto, Alvar (Box 35)
  - Cities (Box 35)
    - Abo (Box 35)
    - Helsinki (Box 35)
      - House of Culture (Box 35)
      - National Institute of Pensions (Box 35)
      - Palace of the Diet (Parliament) (Box 35)
      - Railroad Station (Box 35)
      - Olympic Stadium (Box 35)
      - Theaters (Box 35)
    - Hvittransk (Box 35)
    - Imatra (Box 35)
    - Jyvaskyla (Box 35)
    - Lapua (Box 35)
    - Otaniemi (Box 36)
    - Oulu (Box 36)
    - Paimion (Box 36)
    - Pori (Box 36)
    - Saynatsalo (Box 36)
    - Sunila (Box 36)
    - Tampere (Box 36)
    - Tuppitendas (Box 36)
    - Turku (Box 36)
    - Viipuri (Box 36)
- France (Box 37)
  [Boxes 37-26]
  - General (Box 37)
  - Interiors (Box 37)
  - Landscapes (Box 37)
  - Ornaments (Box 37)
  - Architects (Box 37)
    - General (Box 37)
      - Ecole National Des Beaux-Art (Box 37)
      - French Academy of Architects (Box 37)
    - Baudot, Anatole de (Box 37)
    - Beaudoin, E. (Box 37)
    - Carlu (Box 37)
    - Detournelle (Box 37)
    - Fourier, Charles (Box 37)
    - Garnier, Tony (Box 37)
    - Guimard, Hector (Box 38)
    - Jourdain, F.P. (Box 38)
    - Labatut (Box 38)
    - Le Corbusier (Box 38)
      - Photographs (Box 38)
      - Algiers Plan (Box 38)
      - Cellular System Housing Block (Box 38)
      - Citroham House (Box 38)
      - City for 3 Million (Box 38)
      - Cooperative Village 1934 (Box 38)
      - Skycraper Project (Box 38)
      - Miscellaneous Projects (Box 38)
      - Le Modulor (Box 38)
      - Nemours Plan (Box 38)
      - Paris Museums (Box 38)
      - Patent 226x226x226 (Box 38)
      - Sainte-Beaume (Box 38)
      - Sainte-Die (Box 38)
      - Stadium Project (Box 39)
      - U.S.S.R. Project (Box 39)
      - Ville Radieuse (Box 39)
      - "Voisin" Plan for Paris (Box 39)
    - Lods, M (Box 39)
    - Mallet-Steven, Robert (Box 39)
    - Mopin, E. (Box 39)
    - Percier & Fontaine (Box 39)
    - Perret, A & G (Box 39)
    - Vignon, Barthelmi (Box 39)
    - Viollet-le-Duc (Box 39)
  - Cities (Box 40)
    - Agen (Box 40)
    - Aix-En-Provence (Box 40)
    - Amiens (Box 40)
    - Angers (Box 40)
    - Angouleme (Box 40)
    - Anguell (Box 40)
    - Arles (Box 40)
    - Assy (Haute, Savoie) (Box 40)
    - Audincourt (Box 40)
    - Auteuil (Box 40)
    - Avranches (Box 40)
    - Bar-le-Duc (Box 40)
    - Baules-Les-Pins (Box 40)
    - Bazoches (Box 40)
    - Baeune (Box 40)
    - Blois (Box 40)
    - Boulogne (Box 40)
    - Boulogne Billancourt (Box 40)
    - Boulogne-Surseine (Box 40)
    - Carmaux (Box 40)
    - Chatilly (Box 40)
    - Charleville (Box 40)
    - Cherbough (Box 40)
    - Clichy (Box 41)
    - Compiegne (Box 41)
    - Corsica (Box 41)
    - Domremy (Box 41)
    - Drancy (Box 41)
    - Dreux (Box 41)
    - Elizabeth Ville (Box 41)
    - Eveux-sur-Arbresle (Box 41)
    - Fontainbleu (Box 41)
    - Garches (Box 41)
    - Grancy (Box 41)
    - Guise (Box 41)
    - Herbiers (Box 41)
    - Honfleur (Box 41)
    - Hyeres (Box 41)
    - Issoire (Box 41)
    - Ivry (Box 41)
    - Laon (Box 41)
    - La Rochelle (Box 41)
    - Le Havre (Box 42)
    - Le Mans (Box 42)
    - Le Pradet (Box 42)
    - Le Raincy (Box 42)
    - Le Vesinet (Box 42)
    - Lille (Box 42)
    - Lisieux (Box 42)
    - Lourdes (Box 42)
    - Lyon (Box 42)
    - Macon (Box 42)
    - Maizieres-Les-Metz (Box 42)
    - Malmaison (Box 42)